<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>agilepractices on don&#39;t just talk agile - walk agile!</title>
    <link>https://walkagile.com/tags/agilepractices/</link>
    <description>Recent content in agilepractices on don&#39;t just talk agile - walk agile!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Peter Häfliger</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://walkagile.com/tags/agilepractices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>More Fun with Retrospectives: Check your rearview mirror!</title>
      <link>https://walkagile.com/blog/more-fun-with-retrospectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://walkagile.com/blog/more-fun-with-retrospectives/</guid>
      <description>This is the translation of my blog post written in German as an assignment for the CAS DevOps Leadership and Agile Methods which I am currently doing at the Lucerne University of Applied Sciences and Arts. The translation is rather free, as self-translations usually are, because the author can allow themself full liberties. But let me first explain the context of the course assignment:
During the course, a colleague brought up the question of how shy team members can be encouraged to speak up in a retro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Retrospectives</title>
      <link>https://walkagile.com/blog/funretrospectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://walkagile.com/blog/funretrospectives/</guid>
      <description>This first post is an updated version of an article which I have written in January 2021 for an older blog of mine which I have since discontinued. It was the time when we had to prepare our first distributed/online retrospectives during the Corona lockdown. It describes my experience with Fun Retrospectives, a book, website and very helpful online retro tool.
Introduction For those who do not know the term “retrospective” (or “retro” for short), I cite the following method-independent definition:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
