<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on don&#39;t just talk agile - walk agile!</title>
    <link>https://walkagile.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on don&#39;t just talk agile - walk agile!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Peter Häfliger</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://walkagile.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Backtracking algorithms: experiment, inspect and adapt</title>
      <link>https://walkagile.com/draft/backtracking-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://walkagile.com/draft/backtracking-algorithms/</guid>
      <description>In this post I tell the story of a beautiful picture which represents an interesting mathematical problem whose algorithmic solution has some analogy to the agile way of making progress.
The picture My former highschool math teacher Hansruedi Widmer (&amp;ldquo;retired as a teacher, not as a mathematician&amp;rdquo;) daily posts mathematical puzzles, bits of history or just &amp;ldquo;fun facts&amp;rdquo; on twitter. On March 1st, 2022, which was the 60th day of the year, he tweeted the following (translation from German is mine):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why names in programs matter</title>
      <link>https://walkagile.com/draft/why-names-in-programs-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://walkagile.com/draft/why-names-in-programs-matter/</guid>
      <description>I would like to play around a bit with the go programming language. It is not a bad idea to learn a new programming language every once in a while to get to know different ways of thinking about computational problems. I did that extensively in the first years of my professional career when I was working abroad and had a lot of time during my lonely hotel nights. I do it very little today where I prefer to spend my free time with my family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Table of pairs whose sum is one of the given square numbers</title>
      <link>https://walkagile.com/materials/blog/backtracking-algorithms/table-pairs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://walkagile.com/materials/blog/backtracking-algorithms/table-pairs/</guid>
      <description>The following table lists all 93 pairs which can be formed with the numbers from 1 to 60 whose sum is an element of the set {9, 36, 49, 64, 81}:
 The first column lists the numbers i from 1 to 60. The second column lists all the numbers greater than i with which i can be paired. That&amp;rsquo;s the column used by the first (slow) version of the python program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Development as a multidisciplinary endeavor</title>
      <link>https://walkagile.com/blog/software-development-multidisciplinary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://walkagile.com/blog/software-development-multidisciplinary/</guid>
      <description>Last summer I came across an advertisement for a teaching assignment at a swiss university for a module called &amp;ldquo;Software Engineering Basics&amp;rdquo;. I applied and was even invited to an interview, but eventually they chose another candidate with a track record in education. But even if not successful, the application process proved to be a valuable opportunity for learning and self-reflection. When I applied, I knew of course that I lacked the teaching background, but more importantly, I had to ask myself whether I had the necessary domain expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Retrospectives</title>
      <link>https://walkagile.com/blog/funretrospectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://walkagile.com/blog/funretrospectives/</guid>
      <description>This first post is an updated version of an article which I have written in January 2021 for an older blog of mine which I have since discontinued. It was the time when we had to prepare our first distributed/online retrospectives during the Corona lockdown. It describes my experience with Fun Retrospectives, a book, website and very helpful online retro tool.
Introduction For those who do not know the term “retrospective” (or “retro” for short), I cite the following method-independent definition:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
