<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on don&#39;t just talk agile - walk agile!</title>
    <link>https://walkagile.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on don&#39;t just talk agile - walk agile!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Peter Häfliger</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://walkagile.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Software Development as a multidisciplinary endeavor</title>
      <link>https://walkagile.com/blog/software-development-multidisciplinary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://walkagile.com/blog/software-development-multidisciplinary/</guid>
      <description>Last summer I came across an advertisement for a teaching assignment at a swiss university for a module called &amp;ldquo;Software Engineering Basics&amp;rdquo;. I applied and was even invited to an interview, but eventually they chose another candidate with a track record in education. But even if not successful, the application process proved to be a valuable opportunity for learning and self-reflection. When I applied, I knew of course that I lacked the teaching background, but more importantly, I had to ask myself whether I had the necessary domain expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Retrospectives</title>
      <link>https://walkagile.com/blog/funretrospectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://walkagile.com/blog/funretrospectives/</guid>
      <description>This first post is an updated version of an article which I have written in January 2021 for an older blog of mine which I have since discontinued. It was the time when we had to prepare our first distributed/online retrospectives during the Corona lockdown. It describes my experience with Fun Retrospectives, a book, website and very helpful online retro tool.
Introduction For those who do not know the term “retrospective” (or “retro” for short), I cite the following method-independent definition:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
