<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>devops on don&#39;t just talk agile - walk agile!</title>
    <link>https://walkagile.com/tags/devops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in devops on don&#39;t just talk agile - walk agile!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Peter Häfliger</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://walkagile.com/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>don&#39;t just say the same, mean the same - how to overcome linguistic silos</title>
      <link>https://walkagile.com/blog/linguistic-silos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://walkagile.com/blog/linguistic-silos/</guid>
      <description>This is a transcript of the ignite talk which I have given at the DevOpsDays Vilnius 2025 last week.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what an ignite talk is, you might want to check out my previous article about my first such talk given at the DevOpsDays Zürich last year where I explain the format and how to best prepare for it.
I had a great two days at this event which was perfectly organized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>wholesome talk - language patterns for feedback and learning</title>
      <link>https://walkagile.com/blog/wholesome-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://walkagile.com/blog/wholesome-talk/</guid>
      <description>This article is about the ignite talk which I have given at the DevOpsDays Zurich 2024 earlier this week.
I had never spoken at any conference before. As a product owner and former scrum master, I am used to facilitating events with my team or presenting to customers. In such informal settings, the speaker usually speaks freely and abuses the slides as notes to remember what they want to say. That&amp;rsquo;s why most such slides contain much too much text.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
